Sherry Liao

CONTACT

(778) 345-6789 fanhsuanliao@gmail.com fanhsuanliao.com 8808 168 ave, Burnaby, V4Y 7G6

EDUCATION

Third Year Interactive Arts + Technology Simon Fraser University Jan, 2015 - Jun, 2021 (expected)

Langley Fundamental Middle and Secondary School / 2012 - 2015

SKILLS

Visual Design
Art Direction
Branding Strategy
3D Model Animation
2D Motion Typography

TOOLS

Maya Sketch + Flinto HTML/ CSS Adobe After Effect Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop

INTERESTS

Piano Basketball Hand doodling

LANGUAGES

English (fluent)

Mandarin (native)

Japanese (beginner)

PROFILE

I am a self-motivated motion graphic designer and 3D modeler who is passionate about crafting memorable visual experience that evokes emotional responses and awareness. With all of my work, I aim to use creative storytelling and strong strategic thinking through the design process to create meaningful digital projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Ability to work under pressure and produce portfolio- quality motion graphics with the strong understanding of 2D and 3D animation principles via digital software.

TRANSFERABLE SKILLS

Teamwork: demonstrated confidence and a collaborative attitude with other team members as well as the ability to work independently in a self-directed environment, and comfortable with receiving, giving and implementing design feedback.

EXPERIENCE

Woking Chinese Restaurant

Hostess / Oct, 2015 - Sep, 2017

Greeted the customers, organized the seating arrangement, presented the clean menu to customers, assisted the server and maintained the friendly atmosphere during the dining service.

INVOLVEMENTS

Langley Lodge Senior Home

Volunteer for the Foundation of Tzu Chi / July, 2013 - May, 2016

Volunteered to serve snacks and assist the senior people in eating without spilling on themselves, accompanied them during the bingo game to bring joy to the elderly on every second week of a month.

North Surrey Secondary School

Mandarin Teaching Assistant for the Foundation of Tzu Chi / July, 2013 - Aug, 2015

Volunteered as a TA in grade three Mandarin class to assist the class including emailing their parents about the homework instruction, grading the students' quizzes, and informing their parents for upcoming in-class activities on every summer from the first week of July to the third week of August.

Langley Fundamental Middle and Secondary School

Math Peer Tutor / Sep, 2013 - Jan, 2014

Integrated an active learning method to improve student's weakness by exploring different teaching methods to encourage them to face their challenge.